Keep runnin' along.
Watch as we pass by.
As we raise our flag.
Up high in the sky.
Alright, here we go now.
Sailing through the endless ocean.
Facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure.
Nobody has ever.
Got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep
believing in our dreams.
And let our heart lead the way.
Then once we got all that.
All there's left is to go.
When we face the dark and stormy weather.
Keep the pace.
We'll link our hearts together.
Then I'm sure we'll make it through.
No matter what.
Keep running along, keep running along.
Still raising our flag as we journey on.
Though our chances are close to none.
We won't back down from anyone.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
Toward our own dreams
while keeping the pace.
With a compass pointing to our goal.
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world.
Start me up.
Keep running along, keep running along.
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top.
There's no way that we'll ever quit.
We'll keep heading for tomorrow.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
I see through your eyes,
what we'll have to face.
All the memories will stay in our hearts.
We'll never let them go.
Brand new world.
Start me up!
All right, we pulled the lever!
Bring down the bridge!
Looks like Mozu took care
of things on her side, too.
Go, Swahad!
Look, the drop ridge is lowering!
Our reinforcements pulled
it together, after all.
And just in time, too.
I'm dribbling with excitement.
Come on, hurry up.
Looking scary there, Zoro.
Hey, Robin!
We'll save you, no matter what!
Stay away!
They're in high spirits.
They sure got Gotspartan down our flag.
They're just idiots.
They dug their graves the
second they set foot here.
No! Stay over there!
That garden stole Straw Hat!
The rest is up to you!
Damn you pirate scum!
We'll never let you through!
Prepare the mortar cannon!
Don't let him cross the bridge
even if you have to destroy it!
Yes, sir!
No way I'm gonna let you do that!
Five heads nice!
You've got three heads too many!
Dismantle our shop!
Chief Justice Baskerville, no!
Sike!
Jokes on you!
We're actually the Chief Justice Trio!
Known as the left Baskerville,
my true name is Bass.
Known as the right Baskerville, My
name is Kerr-Vill And as for me,
the center Baskerville Call me
Vincent What is wrong with you?
You mean all this time it was
three dudes stuck together?
Why would they do that?
Cause we're the best of friends?
That's just weird!
Now fire the trench mortar.
What happened?
Why'd it stop?
Damn those marines!
They really pissed me off!
Stop getting in the way!
We got it, Chief Spandam!
Evaculate the Tower of Law!
Good work!
And also, good advice!
This should buy me enough time
to get to the Gates of Justice!
Alright, move it!
Someone grab Cutty Flamm
and bring him too! Robin!
They're nobodies.
Just a bunch of scum.
As long as I've got CP9 here,
I'm practically invincible.
Better yet, I've got the only person who
can revive the ancient weapons, Nico Robin.
Not to mention the man who inherited
one of their blueprints, Cutty Flamm.
I'm not letting this
slip through my fingers.
I'll crush as many pirates as it takes!
What?
What the hell is it?
Is that...?
No, it can't be.
Those aren't the real
blueprints for Pluton.
Oh, they're real!
Don't believe me.
Luchi, Kaku.
You guys can tell, right?
Suppose we should have seen this coming
If you can hide soda and
weapons in your body,
you can hide blueprints just as easily.
So, they are real?
They're really real?
That's great!
Then hand them over!
Saves me the trouble
of searching for them!
Nico Robin.
I gotta admit, the rumors I heard about
you were about as wrong as they could be.
While the government was
dragging us to this crap hole.
I realize that you
aren't the monster that's
going to use the ancient
technology for evil.
I know the shipwrights from
Water 7 have been passing
down these blueprints from
generation to generation.
But we're not doing it to revive a weapon.
Tom had achieved so many wonderful things,
but he gave up everything to keep
these blueprints hidden from the world.
As long as the risk
remains that a woman named
Nico Robin can figure out
how to restore the weapon,
then the world needs these
blueprints to be able to fight back.
Hey, Spanda.
The reason why Tom and Iceberg risked
their lives to protect this is simple.
Just give me the blueprints.
If an ancient weapon fell into the hands
of some power-hungry dumbass like you,
who knows what might happen?
In other words,
the shipwrights passed this
blueprint down to create
a possible countermeasure
against another weapon.
Now, I agree that Robin's
a dangerous woman.
As long as people like you
were around even if she has the
best intentions her knowledge
could still be used to wreak
havoc on the whole world but
now she's got friends who are
willing to risk their lives to
make sure that never happens and
I think they're up to the job
so I'm making a bet now that
everything's gone to hell I
have to get a little creative if
I'm gonna uphold the wishes of
the original architects just
shut up and hand them over
already those blueprints are mine.
Tom if you were here I'm
sure you'd do the same thing
What the hell are you doing? No!
No!
My dream, it's been burned to a crisp.
We spent five years on
our mission for this.
The only reason we were keeping those
blueprints was to create a countermeasure.
So if you took them away,
that would defeat the purpose.
Now that it's come to this,
destroying them is all I can do.
But I'd rather sacrifice my own
plan than help you with yours.
If you end up making a weapon after all,
we won't be able to fight back anymore.
And that's possible if you're able to take
Nico Robin through the Gates of Justice.
Everything's resting on the Straw Hats.
And if they're able to get her out of here,
then you'll be left with nothing at all.
I've placed my bet.
I think they can do it.
You've made a mockery
of me for the last time!
Laugh it up while you can, because
you're not leaving this island alive?
Big bro!
Hey, look!
We're all down here, big bro!
Guys, big bro's right over there.
That means we're not too late!
You're right, I can see him!
Don't worry, we'll save
you no matter what!
We came with the Straw Hats!
Sodom and Gomorrah fought hard too!
We're all going home together, I promise!
They didn't hurt you, did they?
What?
No way!
Oh, damn it, you guys!
I didn't ask you to save me!
I didn't ask you!
But you still came!
I'm not crying, you hear me,
you bastards, I'm not crying.
Shut up, that's enough!
Whoa, Luffy, calm down.
Robin's waiting, hurry up
and bring down the bridge.
Oh, yeah, right, what the
hell are you waiting for?
No kidding!
Get moving already!
Don't make me come down there!
Uh, yes, ma 'am.
Well, Nami, you're sexy
when you boss people around.
Hey, Straw Hat!
Thanks for helping out
my men while I was gone.
But now that the gang's all here,
the one and only Franky will show
you how super his gratitude can be.
I don't need your help!
I'm still mad about what you did to
Usopp, so don't think we're friends!
He's, uh, right next to you, ain't he?
Cutty Flam.
How dare you burn my blueprints?
I'm gonna make you pay.
Big Bros falling down the waterfall!
Franky!
Hey, stop!
Huh? Granny Kokoro?
I heard everything.
Why are you all just standing around?
We're not standing around.
The bridge broke.
There's no way over.
It's halfway down, isn't it?
That's more than enough.
Hang on.
I'll be there in about four seconds.
Jump into the waterfall.
Give it all you've got. Trust me.
Boy, look.
Here he comes.
Monster Granny?
What did she say?
Well, she said, jump into the waterfall.
Holy crap! Is that a train?
What's it doing inside the courthouse?
Chimney, sound that whistle
as loud as you can! Okay!
Ya-ya!
Look, it's the Sea Train!
Hey, what's up with that devious chuckle?
They've got this!
Get out of the way!
Don't you dare!
Let's go!
Rocket Man's as fast
as the day it was made.
I'm going to show you
why Tom's Workers is the
most legendary shipbuilding
company in the world.
Is that Rocket Man?
It's flying!
Please go away!
Water Ball!
Ha-ha!
Brings back memories, don't it, Tom?
Giving a hand to that Roger guy
is something I'll never forget.
In fact, it's something
I take great pride in.
My name's Loopy, and I'm going
to be king of the pirates.
Really? Yep.
That boy may have a screw loose, but
come to think of it, so did Roger.
It's funny.
All those years ago, you helped him out.
And now Tom's workers is coming together
again to help out this Straw Hat boy.
We sure didn't learn our lesson, did we?
But I got a feeling you would
have done the same thing, Tom.
We're gonna crash!
Hey, what the hell are we doing?
No way!
No!
Damn it!
You're coming with me!
If only I could figure out a
way to get these handcuffs off.
All right, I'm letting
you guys off the chain!
Now go give them hell?
I want you to smackle the walls of the
town of law with the guts, you hear me?
You've got full authority to butcher them!
Protecting me is your
one and only priority.
Got it?
Where's Funfrey?
There, good boy.
I've got CP9 on my side, and I've
got my trusty elephant sword.
As long as I maintain my cool,
there's nothing that can stop me.
Now, we're off to the Gates of Justice.
If you really think you can take this woman
from me, go ahead and try it, Straw Hat!
Big Bro Franky is alive!
The Straw Hats actually made it across!
They finally did it!
Big Bro is free at last!
And he's gonna join the fight!
Hell yeah!
Our bro is one hell of a guy!
Go get him, Franky!
Take him down!
Go Straw Hats!
The rest is in your hands, Straw Hats!
Hey, talk to me! You guys okay?
Come on, you old hag!
Start moving and just what the
hell do you think you're doing?
Pulling a flat-out stupid stunt
with Rocket Man like that?
I mean, thanks for saving us and all.
Hey, you hear me? Get up!
Please, don't die!
Don't die, you old hag!
Bloody gongers!
You're damn lucky, you bloody
nose, is all you've got!
Oh, boy!
We made it!
Guess he's fine.
Thanks for the ride
across, Monster Granny!
Come on, you guys, get up already!
You've been through worse than that!
Oh, sure, that's easy for you to say.
You're made out of rubber.
We're lucky we're not in pieces
right now after a crash like that.
See, you're all just fine.
You know, you guys are a bunch of weirdos.
It felt like I should point that out.
There's a staircase over there.
We'd better move it if
we're gonna find Robin.
Not so fast!
What the hell is that?
So you've invaded the Tower of Law.
There's no point in going on.
You won't ever find Nico Robin.
Luchi's already taken her
to the Gates of Justice.
Oh, and the chief's with them, too.
Hmm. Really?
Thanks for telling us where
we should start looking.
Chababa, why'd I tell them that?
He's not too bright.
It doesn't matter.
I might have told you
where they're headed,
but I'm not gonna tell
you how to get there?
and you'll never make
it past our CP9 agents.
We've been given direct orders
to eliminate you, Chapa-Bah.
Did he say eliminate us?
You want Nico Robin?
Then you're gonna have to
fight your way through each
and every one of our agents
if you want to succeed.
Duh!
I liked it better when you were telling
us things we didn't already know.
Chapa-Bah, you've got some fire in you.
But I've got one more thing to
tell you. Say it. We're listening.
Uh, well, thank you.
Now, give me just a sec.
Take a look at this.
A key?
What's it for?
For all you know,
it might be the key needed to unlock
Nico Robin's C-PRISM Stone handcuffs.
C-PRISM Stone?
It's a stone that nullifies a
person's Devil Fruit abilities.
It's basically the same as
when they fall into the ocean.
Well, now we finally know why
Robin hasn't been fighting back.
I knew it wasn't adding up.
Yeah, she's not the
type to give up so easy.
I'm sure she'd be mopping the floor with
their ugly mugs if she had the choice.
She must feel so helpless.
Well, that sucks.
Even if you were able to get past us
and save her in some imaginary world,
that C-prism stone is
tougher than a diamond.
She'd have to live with them on her
wrists for the rest of her life.
Why do I keep telling them this stuff?
He really is dumb, isn't he?
So be my guest.
Go try to save her if you think you can.
Fuck!
Give me that key!
Guess all the CP9 guys can use that move.
Don't be hasty.
You don't even know if this is
the actual key I've got here.
You have got to be freaking kidding me!
It might be a key to another
pair of cuffs For all you know,
cha-ba-ba-ba-ba!
In this great tower of law.
There are five members
of CP9, including me.
And each and every member
has a very own need.
So let's get in the game, hide and seek.
So you're saying we gotta
beat each one of you guys.
And then try every key on our handcuffs.
And that's the only way we're
gonna find the real one.
What a stupid way to keep us busy.
While we're wasting time
on your key hunting game.
Your chief is gonna
escape through those gates
with Rob retrieving Robin
is our first priority?
If we focus on getting Robin back first,
we can worry about the key is afterward.
Let's just ignore that
weirdo and start searching
Hey, you've got some brains,
but I'm afraid if you do that,
then you'll leave me with no choice?
I'll toss this kid to the ocean!
We're kind enough to give
you guys a sporting chance.
See ya.
Hey, get back here!
Hold on, Luffy.
Will you just wait a second?
Stop running and listen to me.
Let's decide what we're going
to do before we split up.
Shut up and let me go!
Get a hold of yourself, Straw Hat.
I'm guessing Luchi's that pigeon guy.
Yeah, that's him.
From what that freak told us, he's the
only one they've got guarding Robin.
Our best bet's to send Luffy after him.
Luffy, since you're raring to go,
you can hunt down that pigeon guy.
Where we go? Where we go?
Excluding Luffy, we've
got a head count of six.
He said there are only
five CP9 agents with keys.
So I say we spread out, take them
down, and catch up with Luffy.
If they drag her across those
gates, we'll never get her back!
It's a race against time!
Then let's get going!
Take him down, or we die
trying. Yeah! Good luck!
Go, pirate guys, go!
You can do it!
Huh?
Chimney? Gombe!
Where did those two disappear to?
They must have taken Robin this way!
They couldn't have gotten too far ahead!
I'm not gonna let them take you
through the Gates of Justice, Robin!
There's no help for you, Nico Robin!
You can keep wishing for them to come,
but they'll never find their
way to the Gates of Justice!
AHAHAHA, AHAHAHA!
AHHHHH!
QUIT HIDDING FROM ME,
YOU PIDGEON-LOVING JERK!
I gotta find the kitchen
before I do any more fightin'!
I'm in serious trouble if I don't...
CUDABOO!
I need a bottle and a half of
cola to properly fuel Cudaboo,
and I've already managed to go through
a little more than two of them today!
I gotta nab at least three full
bottles if I'm gonna take on CP9!
Huh? There!
That's got to be the kitchen!
You've come face-to-face with
the gossip-loving silent Fukuro!
I suppose you want my keys!
Great, just move where I
can refill my cola! Zappa!
No one in there.
Nope.
Not in there.
I'm empty.
What's the deal?
I can't find anyone around here.
Not that I really mind.
Ah, so you're too afraid to freeze the m -
It's not him!
He's asleep?
Is he with CP9?
What?
He just let the key out
while he's taking a nap?
My luck couldn't possibly
be this good, could it?
This is a golden opportunity.
What is this place?
It looks like some kind of dungeon.
Your hopeless quest for
your friend's freedom
has doomed you to die a
dreadful death by my hand!
Do you hear my words?
You're doomed.
I said you're doomed. Doomed.
Doomed. OOOJU!
YOYOY!
Geez, he's allowed.
This room better not be empty!
Damn it!
Getting real tired of this.
What's wrong? Just relax.
Tell you what.
I'll put on some tea.
Well, that sounds wonderful.
Your swords are drawn.
You don't waste time!
They've been thirsty
for the taste of blood?